[HORSE NEIGHS]
芭比姐妹之小马故事
[HONKS HORN THEN SIGHS]
啊！我们到了
We made it.
[SEBASTIAN SNORES
THEN POPCORN BARKS]
[SEBASTIAN YELPS THEN BARKS]
我要走 我要走！我要走！
CHELSEA: I gotta go, I gotta go.
-Last one out's a rotten cheese.
最后下车的是臭奶酪！
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
[BREATHES DEEPLY]
Just breathe that air. Very Alpsy.
快呼吸这空气！非常阿尔卑斯
Look, look, horses. Let's go riding.
看！看！马儿！
我们去骑！请问我们可以吗？
- Can we please? Can we?
-Chelsea, chill.
我们可以吗？
切尔西 冷静 我们有整月时间骑马
-We've got all month to ride the horses.
SKIPPER: Whoa.
哇！
BARBIE:
I know, it's the Matterhorn. Isn't it amazing?
我知道！是马特峰！难道不叹为观止吗？
No, I mean this LCD screen.
不 我是说液晶屏
Thirty-three megapixel resolution
with 24.7 million colours.
33兆像素分辨率 24.7百万色彩！
- It's like we're there.
-Ha-ha. Skipper, we are there.
就像我们身临其境！
斯基珀 我们是身临其境
Oh, yeah, nice mountains.
But on this baby, I can zoom in.
哦 对 奇峰
但在这宝贝上我还能放大！
MARLENE: Barbie.
-Aunt Marlene.
芭比！
玛琳姨妈！
MARLENE:
Skipper. Stacie.
斯基珀！
斯塔西！
Chelsea.
切尔西！
Welcome to the Alpine Riding Academy.
欢迎来到高山马术学校！
BARBIE: Thank you so much
for having us here.
[GIRLS CHATTERING]
-Hello, Barbie.
-Hello, Max.
好 芭比
- 你好 麦克斯
- 芭比！
MARIE: Barbie.
-Whoa!
哇！
-Oh, Marie.
-Hi, Marie.
哦 玛丽！
- 嗨 玛丽！
- 真的来了！
- You're really here.
-Please excuse my sister.
请原谅我妹妹 她是被松鼠养大的
-She was raised by squirrels.
MARLENE: I'm so glad you're all here.
我好高兴们都来了！
请进屋
Please, come inside.
Barbie, I love the hand-tooled
detail on your luggage.
芭比 我爱行李箱上手工打造的细节 非常漂亮
- It's awfully smart.
BARBIE: Thanks.
多谢
I got a suitcase just like it.
Except mine is covered with scorpions.
我有个手提箱像这一样！
除了我的上面覆盖着蝎子
[SUITCASE THUDDING]
[DOORKNOB RATTLING AND
KIDS GRUNTING & CHATTERING]
让路！
-Ooh.
-Whoa.
哦！
This is it.
就是这
The flowers were my little touch.
这鲜花是我的小小点缀
-And I picked off most of the bugs.
-Most of the bugs?
而且我挑去了大多数虫子
大多数虫子？
Oh, and I put sweets on all
of your pillows just like in a hotel.
哦 我还在们枕头上放了糖果 就像住宾馆！
Oh. Of course, that was three days ago
and some of them melted...
哦 当然 是三天前放的
有些融化了 其余的被爆米花花吃了
...and Popcorn ate the rest...
...but you can still smell them when you sleep.
但们睡觉时还能闻香入梦
MARLENE: Thank you, children.
MARIE: Popcorn.
- 孩子们 谢谢了
- 爆米花花！
MARLENE:
Now back to your chores.
- 回去忙你们的事吧
-I got dibs on the top bunk.
-No, me.
我有权睡上铺！
不 我！
BOTH:
One, two, three, shoot.
石头剪刀布！
-Yes.
-No.
- 爽！
- 不！
[HORSE NEIGHS]
The room's perfect, Aunt Marlene,
and I can't wait to find my horse.
房间很完美 玛琳姨妈
我等不及要寻觅我的马儿了！
CHELSEA:
Your champion horse.
的冠军马！芭比将骑它赢得
Barbie's gonna win
the Pacific Steeplechase with it.
帕西菲克越野障碍赛马！
- Well, I don't know about that. Heh.
SKIPPER: Of course you'll win.
呃 我对那没有把握
当然会赢
You're only the best rider on the West Coast.
就是西海岸最好的骑手
Thanks, but that depends a lot
on finding just the right horse.
多谢 但很大程度上要看找到了好马
The horse of your dreams, hmm?
Every rider has one.
的梦想之马 嗯？
每位骑手都有一匹
Something like that.
像这样的马
Well, I believe we raise the finest jumping horses
in all of Switzerland.
好 我相信我们养了全瑞士最好的跳马
I'm certain you'll find one here
that's to your liking.
我保证会在此觅得如意爱马
Have you got one that looks like this?
有一匹像这样的马吗？
- My. That's quite a horse.
-Isn't it?
哇 真是骏驹
不是吗？
-I hope I brought enough glitter.
-When can we get started?
我希望我带了足够多的闪光贴贴
我们什么时候能开始？
MARLENE: How about now?
STACIE: Yay!
现在如何？
- 耶！
- 喔嗬！
CHELSEA: Whoo-hoo!
-Let's go.
我们走！
Skipper? Don't you want to see the horses too?
斯基珀？不想也来看马吗？
You guys go ahead. I need to update my blog.
们走先 我需要更新我的博客
You used to love horses.
过去好爱马 小时候我们不能拽下马
When you were younger,
we couldn't get you off them.
Well, I guess people change...
呃 我猜女大十八变
...and right now, all my peeps are at TechCon...
现在我是技术控 在体验最新潮设备
...trying out the latest gear...
...while I'm stuck here listening to cows yodel.
当困在这儿听奶牛哼山歌的时候
[cow MOOS]
So first time on a horse, is it?
第一次骑马 是吧？
Yeah, it's my first...
对 是我的第一次
...but it won't take me long to ace it
like I do every sport.
但我玩转它用不了多久 就像我玩每项运动一样
Still, you might want to go slowly at first.
但是 可能想开始慢点
Thanks, but not too slow.
多谢 但不会太慢了
Did I mention I'm kind of a natural jock?
我提到过我天生是赛马手(笑料)吗？
Yes.
对 我们一开始就发现了
We caught it the first time.
We'll match Chelsea and Stacie
with their horses first.
我们先给切尔西和斯塔西找马
Girls, meet your teachers.
姑娘们 见们的老师
Ooh. I want that one or that one.
Can I have two?
哦 我想要那匹！或那匹！我能有两匹吗？
Can we pick whichever horse we want'?
我们能随便挑想要的马吗？
MARLENE:
No, no, ch茅rie.
不 不 切莉 开始时骑手从不挑马
The beginning riders never pick their horses.
- 嗯？
- 由马儿挑
CHELSEA: Huh?
-The horses pick you.
-Excuse me?
MAX: You'll see.
请再说一遍？
会明白的
Step into the corral and then stand really still.
走进围栏...
然后站着不要动
[NEIGHS]
[HORSE SNIFFS]
- Aww. . . .
-it's okay, Chels.
唉
没关系 切儿
[GRUNTS SOFTLY]
[GIGGLES]
Looks like you've got a new bestie, Stace.
看来交上了位新好友 斯黛
STACIE: What's her name?
-Stacie, meet Pepper.
她什么名字？
斯塔西遇见了胡椒
Nice to meet you, Pepper.
很高兴遇到 胡椒
[SNORTS]
[HORSE APPROACHING]
[NEIGHS]
[SIGHS]
唉
[HORSE SNIFFING]
[SNORTS]
[WHINNIES]
看来也被选中了 切尔西
MARLENE: It looks like you too
have been chosen, Chelsea.
Meet Dash.
遇见了点点
[NEIGHS]
-Where's the rest of her?
MARLENE: I'm afraid that's all there is.
她其余的马在哪？
恐怕全部马都在这了
But Dash is a very sweet pony,
and she seems to really like you.
但点点是匹非常可爱的小马
她看起来真的喜欢
But she's so little.
但她太小了
Why can't I have a big horse like Stacie's?
为什么我不能像斯塔西那样有匹大马？
切尔西 给点点一个机会
Chelsea, give Dash a chance.
骑大马的时间有的是
There'll be plenty of time for big horses
when you're a little bigger.
当长大一点点的时候
嗯
ETIENNE:
Catastrophe. Disaster. Calamity.
大难临头！飞来横祸！无妄之灾！
(法语)令人震惊 恐怖！
[SPEAKING IN FRENCH]
Madame Marlene, we are ruined.
玛琳夫人
我们完了！
What is it this time, Etienne?
这次又怎么了 艾蒂安？
Look at these fly bonnets.
看看这些防蝇帽！
Just look at them.
看看它们！
-So?
-So...
- 怎么了？
- "怎么了？"我订的是紫红色
...I ordered them in aubergine
to match the halters.
好配上辔头！可是看！看！
But look. Look.
Would you call that aubergine?
会叫这紫红色吗？嗯？
-Hmm?
-Uh....
呃 不会？
-No?
MAX: He has a point.
他说到点子上 这确实不叫紫红色
That is so not aubergine.
You see? The child is clearly offended.
瞧？这孩子明显生气了！
How are we supposed to win a tournament
with clashing fly bonnets?
用不搭配的防蝇帽我们还怎么赢得锦标赛？
-Even the flies will be laughing at us.
STACIE: Tournament?
甚至苍蝇也会嘲笑我们！
锦标赛？我爱听
I like the sound of that.
The annual tournament between our academy...
我们学校和所有其它本地骑术学校之间的年度赛
...and all the other local riding schools,
and the prize money is substantial.
奖金可观 今年由我们主办
This year we're hosting.
Hmp! But not if our horses are too embarrassed
to take the field.
但如果我们的马太难堪上不了场怎么赢！
I'd better take care of this.
我最好来处理此事
Max, Marie,
you get Stacie and Chelsea started.
麦克斯 玛丽 你们教斯塔西和切尔西开始
Barbie, you of course
may choose your own horse.
芭比 当然可以选择自己的马
Look over the thoroughbreds in the stable.
过目一遍马厩里的纯种马
Every one's a prize jumper.
每匹都是获奖的跳马
Did you see the stitching?
看见针脚了吗？我特意要求交叉排线缝法
I specifically asked for a cross-hatch stitch.
This is not a cross or even a hatch.
这个既没有交叉线也没有排线...
And did you see the halters they sent?
Who was that?
那是谁？
That was Monsieur Etienne, our riding master.
那是艾蒂安先生 我们的骑师
ls he always like that?
Like he just bit into a lemon.
他总是喜欢那样吗？好像刚咬到了柠檬
Pretty much. He's a good teacher though.
非常像 但他是个好老师
[CHUCKLES]
Go.
走！
Come on, girl. Good girl.
来 姑娘！好姑娘
-She's all yours.
-Hmph.
她完全是的
哼
Okay. So how do I get on this thing?
那么我该怎么做？
Oh, yes, well, before we begin...
啊 对！我们开始前 我想重温
...I thought it might be instructive
to review the history of the English...
英国马史或马术比赛史或马鞍史很有教育意义
...or eventing saddle.
ls that necessary--?
这有必要吗...
Here you'll see the gullet, the cantle,
the girth buckle--
看这是鞍头、鞍尾、肚带扣...
What my brother is trying to say is...
我哥哥想说的是
...stick your foot in here
and throw your leg over the horse.
踩在这然后跃上马
-That's the big thing right there.
STACIE: Got it.
这才是大事
明白了 多谢
-Thanks.
MAX: Right, of course.
对极 当然 谁需要四百年传统？
Who needs 400 years of tradition?
Fine, just jump on and kick her into drive.
很好 只要跳上去踢她快跑
SKIPPER:
Wait.
等等！
First time on a horse? Definitely video-worthy.
首次骑马？绝对值得视频
Look at that style, that con铿dent approach.
看这气派 充满自信的靠近！
As the future champion approaches...
"当未来冠军靠近时 此动物谦卑的臣服于新主人"
...the animal humbly yields to its new master.
[NEIGHS]
Whoa! Uhn!
哇！
[BOYS LAUGHING]
Look. Alpine has a new trick rider.
看！高山有了位新花样骑手！
What do you call that move?
叫它什么动作？
The mud dive?
"嘴啃泥"？
[BOYS LAUGHING]
Whoa!
哇！
[BOYS LAUGHING]
Hey, Marie, if that's your best rider,
our winning streak seems pretty safe.
嗨 玛丽 如果这就是们最好的骑手
我们的胜算看来十拿九稳！
[BOYS LAUGHING]
Oh, yes.
Hey, if you're looking up world's greatest rider,
I'm right here.
嗨 如果在找"世界最伟大骑手" 我就在这
Actually, I was just looking up doofus.
See? Right here.
实际上 我正在找"笨蛋" 看 就在这
[MONKEY GIBBERING]
[BOYS LAUGHING]
She got you good, Jonas.
她拍你拍得好 乔纳斯！
-How droll.
JONAS: Ahem.
好滑稽
[LAUGHING]
MAX: Don't mind them.
-Pbbt!
别理他们
They're from Ecole Montagne,
the riding school just down the road.
他们来自崇山学校 一条路的马术学校
They're just trying to get under our skin
with the tournament coming up.
他们就是想在比赛即将到来时让我们难受
当然 真的无所谓 反正我们总是输
Of course, it doesn't really matter.
We always lose anyway.
Usually to them.
总是输给他们
MAX:
You never know. This year could be different.
世事难料 今年可能不同
Statistically speaking,
we're bound to win within, hmm, 63 years.
统计上讲 我们注定赢...
在六十三年之内
Now that I'm on the team,
we'll cream those creeps.
现在我加入了团队 我们将狠揍这些烂人！
Whoa! Uhn!
哇！喔！
SKIPPER:
Heh. Yep.
没错
- Classic.
MAX & MARIE: Ha-ha-ha.
经典
[HORSES WHINNYING]
[SNORTS]
[NEIGHS]
[SNIFFS]
[CHUCKLES]
[GRUNTS]
[SNORTS]
[HORSE NEIGHS]
[BARKING]
Why, hello, Sebastian.
哇 你好 塞巴斯蒂安
Hello, Popcorn. Now run along.
好 爆米花花
现在走开吧
Sorry, that took so long, Barbie dear.
抱歉我耽误太久了 亲爱的芭比
Monsieur Etienne can be a bit temperamental
at times.
艾蒂安时不时有点...
爱激动
-lno铿ced.
-He's worth it.
我注意到了
他值得小题大做
我们希望他能让我们赢得11年内
We're hoping he can lead us
to our first tournament win in 11 years.
第一次锦标赛冠军
I'm sure you've got lots of good riders.
我肯定培养了很多好骑手
We did once...
我们曾经是的
...but frankly, enrolment has been incredibly low
these last few years.
但坦白说 这几年入学人数低得惊人
So have you found your horse yet?
找到的马了吗？
Everyone in this group is from champion stock.
这批马个个出身于冠军名门
I'm just not sure.
我就是不太确定
This one seems nice.
这匹看起来不错
Ah. Finian. Excellent choice.
啊 芬尼亚 上佳之选！
His sire was the winner of the Virginia Gold Cup,
so he'll be right at home in America.
他父亲是维吉尼亚金杯赛冠军
所以他在美国会如鱼得水
You two would make an excellent team.
你们俩将是金玉良缘
BARBIE:
Hmm. Maybe.
嗯...也许吧
[ROOSTER CROWS]
[GRUNTING]
嗯
[YAWNS]
[BLEATS AND BARBIE SCREAMS]
啊！
[BOTH TALKING INDISTINCTLY]
- 嗯？一头山羊
- 怎么了？
Oh, no, you don't, you grabby goat.
不 你不准 你这贪吃羊！
[ALL YELLING]
Wa key, wa key.
醒醒 醒醒！
Oh, hi, Barnaby.
哦 嗨 巴纳比
You know him?
认识他？他在吃我的毯子！
-He's eating my blanket.
-Yes, he likes wool.
对 他喜欢羊毛 上周他吃了我所有袜子
Last week, he ate all my socks.
It's a miracle he's still alive.
他还活着真是个奇迹
Get him!
[ALL SCREAM THEN GRUNT]
Breakfast in 20 minutes.
Hope you like Kartoffelkuchen.
二十分钟内吃早餐！希望们喜欢土豆饼
[BARNABY BLEATING]
No, no, no, mademoiselle.
不不不不不不 小姐
We swoop with the curry comb, huh?
Not attack. Huh?
是刷马不是伤马 嗯？
Long curving motions.
长曲线运动...
[SPEAKS IN FRENCH]
像这样刷 懂吗？
And swoop, ah, oui.
And swoop. Yes?
刷 懂吗？
Bend the knees and swoop. Ah.
屈膝刷！
Got it, swoop, swoop.
明白了 刷 刷 屈膝...
Bend.Hey.
嗨！
Give me a break. I'm new at swooping.
给我个机会！我刷马是新手！
Perfect. Dash, you're going to be so pretty.
完美！点点 会好漂亮！
Don't you think so, Chelse?
不觉得吗 切儿？
[DASH SNORTS]
Oof!
哦！
[DASH NEIGHS]
-Oh....
-I can't wait to get out...
我等不及要出去领略风舞发飘的滋味
...and feel the wind in my hair.
唉...
[SIGHS]
快点好不
Yippee-ki-yay.
Ow. O-W.
嗷！
O-W
BARBIE:
Hyah.
驾！
Uh-uh. Reign back, Mademoiselle Barbie.
No faster than a walk, please.
退后 芭比小姐！
请像散步一样慢
We must make certain everyone is riding
at the same pace, n'est-ce pas?
我们必须确保人人步调一致 是不是？
[SIGHS]
Whoa.
哇！
[NEIGHS]
Skipper, Stacey, did you see that?
斯基珀 斯塔西 们看见了吗？
-See what?
-That horse.
- 看见什么？
- 那匹马！
What are you talking about?
在说什么？
I guess, nothing.
我猜...没什么
Nothing at all.
根本没什么
- 要甜点吗？想吃什么吗？
- 不要再添给我了！
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
有人想来杯茶吗？嗯？
Now, tell me the truth, Barnaby.
现在老实告诉我 巴纳比
Doesn't clover taste better than wool?
难道三叶草味道不比羊毛更好？
[BLEATING]
Ha-ha. I'm glad you agree.
我很高兴你同意
[DOGS BARKING AND SNARLING]
BARBIE:
That's the horse.
那就是这马！
ETIENNE [SINGING]:
Fais dodo, t'auras du lolo
Maman est en haut
Elle fait des g茅teaux
(法语)她在做蛋糕
Papa est en bas, il fait du chocolat
(法语)爸爸在楼下
(法语)他在做巧克力
Fais dodo, Reynaud mon petit fr茅re
(法语)睡睡睡 雷诺
(法语)我的小弟弟
Fais dodo, t'auras du Iolo
(法语)睡睡睡
(法语)你会快乐无比
[BARBIE CLAPPING
THEN ETIENNE SQUEALS]
哦 芭比小姐 让我吓一跳！
- Mademoiselle Barbie, you startled me.
-I'm sorry.
对不起 我在欣赏你的歌声
I was enjoying your singing.
-So was Reynaud.
-Oh, heh.
雷诺也是
不足挂齿 它让他安静下来
It is nothing. It calms him down.
Monsieur Etienne, may I ask you a question...
艾蒂安先生 我可以问你一个问题吗？
...about the Academy logo.
有关学校徽标的？
LOQQ?
徽标？
-You know, the sign in front, the horse.
-Ah.
你知道的 前面的招牌？那匹马
啊 那个
That. Heh. Well, what can I say?
It is a horse.
我能说什么？就是匹马嘛
Well, yes, of course.
对 当然 但是匹非常不一般的马 你不觉得吗？
But a very unusual horse, wouldn't you say'?
-I mean, those markings.
-Why the interest?
我是说 那花纹
为什么感兴趣？
It's just.... I don't know...
我就是不知道 我觉得好像在哪里见过这马
...I feel like I've seen that horse somewhere.
on. That is highly doubtful.
那可未必
The horse you speak of does not exist.
说的这马不存在
It doesn't? But the sign--
不存在？但是这招牌...
ls of a fable of an ancient herd
called the Majestique.
它是古代传说神兽"真命天马"
They were said to roam wild somewhere
in these mountains.
它们据说放漫于群山万壑某处
The story is that they are descended
from a breed...
据说它们是延续了
千年之久的品种
...created over a thousand years ago...
...especia||y for the princesses
of the Kieburg royalty...
凯博格皇室公主御骑
...and fiercely loyal to them.
对她们忠心耿耿
They protected them from harm...
它们保护她们免遭伤害 公主们也
...and the princesses were just
as devoted and protective of them.
对它们呵护有加
A strong fearless breed.
强壮无畏的品种
They were said
to have such superb jumping skill...
它们据说有超级跳跃能力
...that they almost seemed to fly.
几乎看起来就像飞
They are known by the strange pink streak
in their manes.
它们因在鬃毛上有奇特粉红条纹而闻名
The smartest, the fastest,
the bravest horses ever known to man.
人类曾知道的最聪明的最快的最勇敢的马！
[NEIGHS]
Many doubt that they were ever real...
很难说它们真实存在过
...since none has ever been caught
or even photographed.
因为没有一只曾被抓到 或曾被照下相
-But what about the painting?
-Heh. What of it?
但这画怎么回事？
有什么大不了的？
还有仙女和美人鱼的画呢 不是吗？
There are also paintings
of fairies and mermaids, no?
所以 你觉得真命天马不是真的？
So you don't think the Majestique horses
are real?
Mm. Once, when I was a child, I thought I saw--
嗯...
曾经 我童年时候
我想我看见了...
-Nonsense. Foolish twaddle.
BARBIE: Huh?
无稽之谈！
蠢废话！
You have always believed in fairy tales, Etienne.
你总是相信童话故事 艾蒂安
Philippe. Hmph.
How dare you defile my stable...
菲利普！你怎敢玷污我的马厩！
...you festering boil on a baboon's backside?
你 你这个狒狒屁股上的脓包！
-And you are the hair of a pig's nostril.
-I spit on the toe of your uncle.
你是猪鼻孔里的脏毛！
我吐口水到你叔叔的鞋上！
I stuff your nose with cabbages.
我塞甘蓝到你的鼻孔里！
呃 嗨 我叫芭比
Hi, my name's Barbie.
I gather you two know each other.
我看你俩相互认识
Excuse-moi, mademoiselle.
对不起 小姐
I am Monsieur Philippe, riding master
extraordinaire of L'Ecole Montagne.
我是菲利普先生 崇山学校顶呱呱骑师
(法语)幸会
[WHINNIES]
I speak up only because this pig
of a dog of a mule...
我说话 只不过是因为这猪狗骡子
...fills your head with phooey-hooey.
在给脑袋灌垃圾
There is no such breed as the Majestique
and there never was.
没有什么真命天马品种 从来没有
No horse is that remarkable.
没有马有那么非同凡响
They are merely dumb beasts meant
to serve their masters...
它们不过是沉默畜生
为主人效劳天经地义
...and fear the riding crop.
怕的就是马鞭！
[NEIGHING]
But why do you ask about Majestiques?
Have you seen something?
但为什么问起真命天马？
...
有看见什么？
Me? Um, uh.... Ha-ha.
我？呃...
How could I see something that doesn't exist?
我怎能看见不存在的东西？
Yes, of course, utter foolishness.
对 当然 傻透了！
Etienne, it is chilly.
艾蒂安 天气冷了
- Maman says to wear your sweater.
-Tell her the soup was yummy.
妈妈说穿上你的毛衣
告诉她汤很好喝
PHILIPPE: And how was the baguette?
ETIENNE: I did not receive a baguette.
长棍面包如何？
我没有收到长棍面包
PHILIPPE:
Exactly.
的确
[CHUCKLES]
Hmm. Come on, Finian, let's go home.
嗯
快 芬尼亚 我们回家
[ANIMALS RUNNING
AND LEAVES RUSTLING]
What is it?
怎么了？
[HORSE GROWLS]
[FINIAN NEIGHING]
[GASPS]
哇！
Finian, come back!
芬尼亚 回来！
[GROWLING]
Oh, boy.
哦 天哪
[WOLVES GROWLING]
[GRUNTING]
[HORSE APPROACHING]
[HORSE NEIGHING]
[SNORTS]
[GROWLS]
[NEIGHS]
So you are real. I knew it.
那么是真的！
我就知道！
Thank you.
谢谢
[NEIGHS]
[CLICKS TONGUE THEN WHISTLES]
[SNORTING]
Heh. My hero.
哼 我的英雄
再来
[ETIENNE SPEAKS IN FRENCH]
挺直 斯塔西小姐
Straighten up, Mam'seI/e Stacie.
Legs pressed together, weight forward.
腿夹紧 重心前倾
[ETIENNE SPEAKS IN FRENCH]
(法语)很好
Now pull your horse back to a walk, then stop.
现在掉转马头 然后停
Whoa.
停
停！
Whoa! Whoa! Whoa!
停 停！
Don't you know how to whoa?
不知道怎么停吗？
No, no, no, mam'selle, we do not yank the reins.
不不不 小姐 我们不猛拉缰绳
You will only make her--
只会让她...
Hey, hey, he)?
[STUDENTS LAUGHING]
嗨 嗨 嗨 嗨！
[PEPPER NEIGHING]
[SIGHS THEN SPEAKS IN FRENCH]
唉 (法语)孩子
Aunt Marlene, I need a new horse.
玛琳姨妈
我需要匹新马
Mine is busted.
我的马捣蛋
No, Stacie, Pepper is your horse
and she chose you for a reason.
不 斯塔西 胡椒就是的马
她选是有原因的
Yeah, because she craves
my public humiliation.
对 因为她想要我丢人现眼
She won't do anything I tell her to.
她不做我要她做的任何事
Of course she will. When she wants to.
当然她会做...
在她想做的时候
[NEIGHING]
Tsk, tsk, hyah!
驾！
HVah!
[FINIAN SNORTS]
BARBIE:
I know you're here somewhere.
我知道在这某处...
[HORSE NEIGHING]
[GASPS]
[NEIGHING]
[PANTING THEN NEIGHING]
It's all right.
没事的
Everything's going to be just fine.
一切就会好起来
Let me help you, okay?
让我来帮 好吗？
哇 真的被卡住了 不是吗？
Wow. You really did get stuck, didn't you?
That must hurt.
一定受伤了
[NEIGHING]
Easy girl, easy.
放松 姑娘 放松
That's it.
就这样
[HUMMING]
[SINGING]
Fais dodo, t'auras du lolo
睡睡睡
会快乐无比
Fais dodo, ma petite soeur
睡睡睡
我的小妹妹
Fais dodo, t'auras du Iolo
睡睡睡
会快乐无比
[GRUNTING]
[NEIGHING]
[HORSE GRUNTING]
Oh, you're bleeding.
哦 在流血
I just want to help you. It's okay.
我只想帮
没关系
[HUMMING]
I owe you this for the wolves.
我用这来答谢驱狼之恩
[SNORTING]
You're so majestic.
真是禀姿神武
I think I'll call you Majesty.
我想我要叫...
真命天女-
Okay, one more, Barnaby.
好 多来一张 巴纳比
And this time a little more presidential.
这次更有点总统气派
[HORSE APPROACHING]
Hey, Tech Girl. Ever put that thing down?
嗨 技术妹！
有曾放下过那玩意吗？
Oh, look, Barnaby, you have a visitor.
看 巴纳比 你有客人来了
[BLEATS]
Did you come to have your official portrait taken,
monkey boy?
你是来拿你的官方肖像来了吗
猴小子？
Ooh. That one will look good on a baboon,
don't you think?
哦！这个配在狒狒上会很好看
你不觉得吗？
[BLEATS]
Heh. You may be good with a tablet,
but I'll bet I can outride you any day.
哈！也许擅长玩平板
但我打赌我骑马能胜过 随便哪一天
You're on. I'll bring the bananas.
一言为定！我会拿来香蕉
Right now, I have some work to do
on your portrait.
现在 我要对你的肖像做点加工
See you.
再见！
ls he looking? Don't look.
他在看吗？
别看！
[SWEEPING]
[NEIGHING]
Dinner in a second.
晚餐马上好！
[GRUNTS]
Oh. Chelsea?
哦 切尔西！
嘘 我在躲点点
-Shh. I'm hiding from Dash.
-Oh.
哦
Why are we hiding from Dash?
为什么我们要躲点点？
Because she keeps eating my hair.
因为她老是吃我头发！
It looks fine to me.
我看它平安无恙
Yeah, but she follows me around everywhere...
是的 但她到处跟着我
...and nibbles on my pigtails...
啃我的辫子 口水流我头上到处都是
...and gets horse slobber all over my head.
I see.
我明白了
[SNIFFS THEN GASPS]
-Does your hair smell like candy?
-Marshmallow Tresses Shampoo.
是不是的头发闻起来像糖果？
棉花糖洗发水
My favourite.
我的最爱
It's made with real live marshmallows.
是用真的棉花糖做的！
Ah. Well, that explains it.
好 这就说得通了
-Dash loves marshmallows too.
-She does?
点点也爱棉花糖
她是吗？
Oh, my, yes.
哎呀 是的
In fact, you two have lots of things in common.
事实上
俩有许多共同之处
她爱漂亮丝带和闪闪发光东西
She loves pretty ribbons,
and things that glitter and anything pink.
和粉红色的一切
Perhaps you should give her another chance.
也许应该给她另一个机会
I don't know.
我不知道
She really, really likes you, Chelsea.
她真的真的喜欢 切尔西
And, you know, I bet she'd look wonderful
in sparkly bows.
知道吗 我肯定她戴着闪光蝴蝶结会美呆了
You think?
觉得？
嗯
Hmm. Maybe I could pretty her up.
也许我能让她靓起来
We could start with a manicure
and then braid her hair.
我们首先能给她修甲和梳辫子
哦...
Oh. And then I could use the sparkles,
and then maybe I could give her....
然后我能用闪光贴贴 然后...
[NEIGHING]
嗯？
Hmm?
Hmm.
嗯
[GASPS]
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
Yeah, way to go!
耶！好样的！
I got this.
这个我懂了
Excellent form, Marie, as always.
状态极佳 玛丽 一如既往！
Pity you are too young to compete. Hmm?
可惜太年轻不能参赛 嗯？
Mam'seI/e Stacie, you are next.
斯塔西小姐 是下一个 记住
Remember, you and your mount are as one.
要和的坐骑默契如一
You must be the horse.
必须化为马儿！
[SQUEALS]
啊！
[BOTH CHUCKLING]
Now, allez vous.
(法语)会吗！
[APPLAUDING]
All right. Now we're talking.
好！现在我们在沟通了！
Oh, man, I am so good at this.
哇 我真的好擅长玩这个！
Whoa!
哇！
[WATER SPLASHING]
[PEPPER SNORTING]
呃 讨厌！
Ugh. Yuck.
[CHILDREN LAUGHING]
Mam'seI/e Stacie.
斯塔西小姐
Perhaps I did not explain.
也许我没说清楚
You are supposed to jump
through the hedge with the horse.
应和马一起跳过树篱
[NEIGHING]
SKIPPER: Ha-ha.
And that's for this year's holiday card.
这张做今年的贺节卡
[BOTH LAUGH]
[HORSE NEIGHING]
HVah!
驾！
[PHILIPPE CHUCKLES]
[SPEAKS IN FRENCH]
好 小姐 现在带我去看发现了什么！
Now, show me what you've found.
[WHISTLES]
MAX: It's classical.
MARIE: So boring.
- 这是古典
- 好无趣！
MAX: It's what you see in races.
They put roses on the horses.
瞧比赛中他们在马上佩玫瑰...
我不关心他们干什么
I don't care what they're for.
MAX:
Since mother left it to us to decide...
既然妈妈留给我们决定
...I think the theme for the dance...
我想舞蹈主题应该是"夏日高山报春花"
...sh0u|d be "Alpine Primroses in Summertime."
I was thinking "Robot Samurai."
我想用"机器人武士"
[DOGS BARKING]
What does that have to do with a horse show?
那与马展有关系吗？
What do you think robot samurai ride around on,
skateboards?
你以为机器人武士骑什么？
滑板？
真的？
Really? You can't put a robot on a horse.
不能放个机器人在马上 它会掉下来！
- It would fall off.
MARIE: Why not?
[GRUNTS]
嗯嗯
[WHISTLES THEN COUGHS]
Ahem. Horse.
马！
啊！
[SCREAMS]
[NEIGHING]
[HEAVYNN GATES' "YOU'RE THE ONE"
PLAYING]
Some people say you can't be found
有人说 你不能被发现
你不在身边
You're not around
哦 哦 哦 哦 哦
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Some people say that you're not real
A fairy tale
有人说 你不真实
Some people say that you're not real
童话故事
A fairytale
有人说 你不真实
Some people say that you're not real
童话故事
A fairytale
哦 哦 哦 哦 哦
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
童话故事
A fairytale
哦 哦 哦 哦 哦
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
They say that dreams are for sleeping
他们说梦是用来酣眠
They say that dreams are for sleepin'
I'm wide awake and believing
我完全清醒抱着信念
I'm wide awake and believin'
Open my eyes and see
You're right in front of me
张开眼 我看见
Open my eyes and see
你就在 我眼前
You're right in front of me
张开眼 我看见
Open my eyes and see
你就在 我眼前
You're right in front of me
You're the one
你是缘
You're the one, I've known all along
You're the one
我一直知道
I've known all along
You're the one
你是缘
[LAUGHING]
You're the one, you're all that I want
你是缘
You're the one
你是全部我想要
You're all that I want
You're wild and free,
Strong enough for me
你豪情无限 为我撑起天
You're wild and free, strong enough for me
And what we have will never be undone
我们结下的缘将沧海桑田
哦 哦 哦 你是缘
Oh, ooh, ooh, you're the one
You're the one
像每天破晓的光线
Like the morning each dawn
Like the morning needs the dawn,
You keep me holding on
你保持我心坚
Run away with me
陪我一路远
Oh, what you are to me,
You show me how to see tomorrow
你为我一路牵
The way you are to me
你教我如何看明天
You show me how to see tomorrow
好！
Tomorrow, tomorrow
明天
Tomorrow
[WHOOPING]
You're the one
你是缘
You're the one, I've known all along
You're the one
我一直知道
I've known all along
你是缘
You're the one
Oh, you're the one
哦 哦 哦
Oh, ooh, ooh
你是缘
You're the one
哦 哦 哦
Oh, ooh, ooh
你是缘
You're the one
[NEIGHING]
Where are you taking me?
带我去哪里？
[HORSE NEIGHING IN DISTANCE]
[GASPS]
Oh....
Majestiques, a whole herd of them.
真命天马！一大群！
[NEIGHING]
[ALL NEIGHING]
[TAPPING ON KEYPAD]
[SIGHS]
- Something wrong, Aunt Marlene?
-it's nothing, dear.
有事情不妙吗 玛琳姨妈？
没什么 亲爱的
-Have you had your lunch yet?
-Something is wrong.
用了午餐没有？
有事情不妙
Please tell me.
I'm a teenager so I'll never let this drop.
请告诉我 我朝气蓬勃 所以我绝不会放弃
[SIGHS]
I'm afraid it's nothing you can help with.
我恐怕帮不了什么忙
The fact is, I may have to sell the academy.
实情是我不得不卖掉学校
Sell it? But why?
卖掉？但为什么？
Too many bills, too few students.
账单太多 学生太少
I have tried to hold on, but two weeks ago,
I got an offer for the place...
我已经疲于坚持 而两周前
崇山学校谢内夫人表示愿意买下这里
...from Madame Cheynet of Ecole Montagne.
No doubt Philippe's idea.
无疑是菲利普的主意
He has never forgiven Etienne
for coming here...
他从未原谅艾蒂安来这儿
...and if we don't win the tournament prize money,
I'll have to accept.
如果我们不赢得锦标赛奖金 我不得不接受
You're not gonna do it, are you?
不会真卖吧？
Alpine has been in our family for generations.
高山学校是我们世代的家 我生于斯长于斯
I was born here.
I'd be crushed to lose it...
失去它我会不好受
...but I may have no choice.
但我别无选择
They're giving me until Tuesday
to accept their offer.
他们要我星期二之前答复
Won't winning the race bring in new students?
但就不能赢得比赛招进新学生吗？
Of course, that would be wonderful.
当然 那会好极了！
But truthfully, we haven't won a tournament
in 11 years.
但说真话 我们11年没赢得锦标赛了
This year, you've got a secret weapon,
the Roberts sisters.
今年有个秘密武器
机器人姐妹！
Can you hold off the sale
just until after the tournament?
能拖到比赛后再卖吗？
I can try.
我能试试 但是 斯基珀 说真的
-But, Skipper, really.
-No time to talk.
没时间聊天了！我得去找个姑娘参赛！
I've got to see a girl about a race.
[MAJESTIC NEIGHING]
[SIGHS]
[SKIPPER WHISTLING]
-Way to go, Barbie.
-Skipper.
- 做得好 芭比！
- 斯基珀！
That is one awesome horse.
真是一匹好马！
Oh, Skipper, it was amazing.
We were flying, soaring.
哦 斯基珀 棒极了！我们刚才在飞！
翱翔！这是我一辈子在寻觅的马！
This is the horse I've been looking for all my life.
But you can't say a word about her.
Not until I say so.
但不可以透露她一个字 除非我透露了
-Barbie, something's happened--
-Promise you won't.
芭比 出了事
保证不会！
Pinky pledge-
拉勾勾！
-When exactly are we too old for that?
-Heh. Never.
我们到底什么时候长大到不做这个？
永远长不大！
Okay, my beautiful Majesty, see you tomorrow.
好 我漂亮的真命天女 明天见 现在走吧
Go on now.
Majesty, I like that.
真命天女 我喜欢这个
But look, there's something
I really need to tell you.
但听着 我真的有事要告诉
BARBIE:
Lose the academy? That's terrible.
失去学校？太糟了！
-Poor Aunt Marlene.
-Exactly.
可怜的玛琳姨妈
就是 所以高山学校必须赢得锦标赛
Which is why Alpine has to win this tournament.
I'm even violating my strict anti-involvement policy
by entering dressage.
我甚至违反了我严格的反干预政策
参加了盛装舞步赛
That's perfect. You're fantastic at dressage.
好合适 你的盛装舞步非常出色！
And that's why you have to run
in the steeplechase.
所以得参加越野障碍赛马了
You riding Majesty
would totally demolish the competition.
骑真命天女谁与争锋！
Skipper, I can't. Etienne is riding for Alpine.
斯基珀 我不能 艾蒂安为高山学校赛马 这是惯例
It's tradition.
And besides, Majesty needs to stay a secret...
此外 真命天女需要保密
...at least till I get her back to Malibu.
至少在我带她回马里布之前
A secret? Why?
保密？为什么？
Because Philippe will recognise what she is
and know there must be more like her.
因为菲利普会认出她是什么马
知道一定还有像她这样的马
After we leave, I don't want her herd
hunted down and broken.
我们离开后 我不想她的种群被猎捕或破坏
So Majestiques need to stay a fairy tale.
所以真命天马需要继续作为童话故事
But what about the steeplechase?
但越野障碍赛马怎么办？
What about us winning the tournament
for Aunt Marlene?
我们怎么为玛琳姨妈赢得锦标赛？
Look, Etienne is a champion rider...
听着 艾蒂安是冠军骑手
...and remember, there's more than one event.
记住 不止一个项目
With you doing dressage...
有参赛盛装舞步 我肯定高山学校将如愿以偿
...I'm sure Alpine's got everything they need.
[SEBASTIAN GRUNTING]
[BOTH BARKING]
[WHEELS ROLLING]
Stacie? You're not practising for Saturday?
斯塔西？
你不为星期六练习吗？
Yeah, I don't know.
I'm kind off horseback riding for now.
对 我不 我现在有点不想骑马了
Really? But aren't you signed up
for the cross-country trial?
真的？但不是报名参加了障碍赛吗？
Actually, I was thinking
about dropping out of that.
实际上
我正想退出 这真的不是我的运动
It's not really my thing.
Okay, Stacie, what's wrong?
斯塔西 怎么了？什么时候起不喜欢拼搏了？
Since when don't you like to compete?
Oh, face it, Barbie, I stink at riding.
面对吧 芭比 我停止骑马了
I just don't get it.
I've always aced everything I've tried.
我就是玩不转 我总是玩什么精什么的！
Skateboards, mountain bikes...
滑板啦 山地车啦 尾波滑水啦
空中乘风滑翔啦 跨国摩托车大赛啦
...wakeboarding, sky surfing, motor cross.
So why can't I control a horse?
为什么我就玩不转一匹马？
Stacie, your horse isn't a skateboard.
斯塔西 的马不是一块滑板
She's a living, breathing being
with her own feelings.
她是活的 有呼吸 有她自己的感情
Yeah, she's made her feelings very clear to me.
对 她非常清楚的对我表达了她的感情
Well, maybe you should try to work with her
instead of just trying to control her.
也许应该试着与她共事 而不是试着控制她
Make friends. Find out what she wants.
交朋友 弄明白她想要什么
Make friends with a horse?
Like what, take her to a movie?
与马交朋友？怎么交 请她看电影？
知道我的意思 只要去试试
-You know what I mean. Just try it.
-Ha-ha-ha!
Oh, and these sugar cubes won't hurt.
还有 给点糖块没有害处
Hmm.
Hi, I'm Stacie.
嗨 我是斯塔西！知道 一直想整残的姑娘！
You know, the girl you've been trying to maim.
[GRUNTING]
Here, have some cavities.
给 得点虫洞洞吧
嗨！
Hey, she likes them. Got any more?
她喜欢！还有吗？
[CHUCKLES]
ANNOUNCER: Welcome to the 108th annual
Inter-Academy Equestrian Tournament.
欢迎来到第108届年度校际马术锦标赛！
And as always, we start things off...
一如既往 我们以永远受欢迎的
...with the perennially popular
Pretty Pony Parade.
漂亮小马游行作为开始！
Isn't Dash pretty?
点点漂亮吧？我们都闻起来像棉花糖！
And we both smell like marshmallows.
-Yeah!
-Oh, look at Chelsea.
MARLENE:
Thank you, Ms. Chelsea.
[CROWD CHEERS AND APPLAUDS]
You're up next, Skipper. We're all behind you.
下一个上场 斯基珀 我们都为加油！
JONAS:
Hey, Tech Girl.
嗨 技术妹 不要告诉我找到个骑马的应用
Don't tell me you've found an app
for riding that thing.
No app needed.
We're doing this strictly old school.
不需要应用 我们严格做个守旧派
ANNOUNCER:
Next up in the Dressage Competition...
接下来盛装舞步赛上场的是
...riding for Alpine, Skipper Roberts on Juniper.
高山学校骑手 骑朱尼珀的斯基珀・罗伯茨
[CROWD CHEERING
AND APPLAUDING]
[LOUD & PROLONGED
CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
ANNOUNCER: And first place goes
to Ms. Skipper Roberts of Alpine.
第一名是高山学校斯基珀・罗伯茨小姐！
[CROWD CHEERS AND APPLAUDS]
嘘！
[BOYS BOOING]
Hmm. Perhaps I should acquire
one of those tablets.
也许我应该搞个平板
ANNOUNCER: Our next event will be
the Cross-Country Competition.
下一个项目是障碍赛
Stacie Roberts on Pepper now,
heading for the double rails at number seven.
骑胡椒的斯塔西・罗伯茨现在正驰往七号双栏
And the jump is good.
精彩一跳！
[ALL CHEER]
现在接近八号 灯塔
ANNOUNCER:
Now approaching jump eight, the Lighthouse...
immediately followed by the Fickle Frank
at number nine.
紧接着是九号腊肠
A smooth landing for Ms. Roberts and Pepper.
罗伯茨小姐和胡椒平稳着地
Moving strongly now
and they beautifully adapt to the corners.
现在跑得更迅猛了 她们出色的应付了拐角
Now jumping over the brush fence at 10.
现在 跳过十号刷篱！
[CROWD MURMURING]
Uh-oh. A run-out.
That will cost them points.
哟 怯场 会让她们扣分
但她们漂亮的克服了 奔向三条！
But they recover nicely and go for the triple bar.
利落的一跳 现在最后最有挑战性的一跳 锁孔！
A clean jump.
Heading now for the final
and most challenging jump, the Keyhole.
Okay, we're friends now, right?
好 我们现在是朋友了？我们这次一起完成这一跳
We go through this jump together this time.
Not just me.
别仅仅是我
Pretty please?
美女好吗？
ANNOUNCER:
A perfectjump.
完美一跳！
[CROWD APPLAUDS]
SKIPPER:
Way to go, Stacie!
Good show, Pepper.
ANNOUNCER:
And here comes the judge's decision.
裁判结果出来了
First place, Stephanie Coda and King's Cross
of Ecole Montagne.
第一名 崇山学校的斯蒂芬妮・柯德和国王十字！
[CROWD CHEERS AND APPLAUDS]
[LAUGHING]
ANNOUNCER: In second place,
Stacie Roberts and Pepper of Alpine.
第二名 高山学校的斯塔西・罗伯茨和胡椒！
ETIENNE: Magni铿que, Stacie.
BARBIE: Good job, Stacie and Pepper.
ETIENNE: Good job, Pepper.
MARIE: You guys were awesome.
Second place, not bad.
第二名？不坏 但下一年 我们要大败他们
But next year, we hammer them.
[NEIGHING]
ANNOUNCER: And that concludes
the opening day competitions...
开幕日比赛结束
...with Ecole Montagne and Alpine Academy
tied for first place.
崇山学校和高山学校并列第一
Tomorrow, the final event...
明天 最后的项目 盛大的
越野障碍赛马将在柏瓦德赛道举行
...the spectacular Steeplechase
at Bernwald Racetrack.
And don't forget the Inter-Academy
formal dance tonight...
别忘了今晚的校际正式舞会 就在高山学校举行！
...right here at Alpine.
That's the best we've done in years.
What a great day for Alpine.
这是多年来我们的最好成绩
高山学校辉煌的一天！
And a long one at that.
也是漫长的一天
I suggest we all have a little rest
before the dance.
我建议我们在跳舞前都休息一会
BARBIE: Where's my blue petticoat?
SKIPPER: My shoes shrunk.
- 我的蓝裤袜在哪里？
- 我的鞋子缩水了！
[CHATTERING INDISTINCTLY]
Nobody move. Oh. How does my hair look?
谁也别动
我的头发如何？
-You're too little for lipstick.
-No fair.
- 抹口红太小了！
- 不公平！
-Aah!
ALL: Barnaby!
- 巴纳比！
- 我的鞋！
STACIE:
My shoe.
[BLEATS]
Might as well throw him the other one.
Maybe he can chew it to match.
可以把另一只也扔给他 也许他能啃出相配的
呃 这个看起来有趣吗？
MARIE:
Em, does this look funny?
[CHATTERING]
STACIE: Look up.
BARBIE: Use the eye shadow.
塞进去！
SKIPPER: Tuck it in.
-Turn around.
转身！
[ALL SIGHS]
[IN UNISON]
Much better.
好多了
ls that...? ls that me?
是吗 是我吗？
I love it.
我喜欢！
[GIGGLES]
Would you like a glass of punch?
It's very tasty.
想喝一杯潘趣酒吗 很美味
There you go. And one for you.
There you go. Would you like some?
给 给你一杯 给 你想要点吗？
Yes, all right.
好吗？好的
-I like the decorations.
MAX: Oh, how are you?
哦 好？
- I know, isn't beautiful?
-it's good to see you again.
我知道 难道不美吗？
很高兴再见到你
Good evening, Etienne.
晚上好 艾蒂安
[SPEAKS IN JAPAN ESE]
空你级哇 这是武士说你好！
-That's "hello" in samurai.
-Oh!
[PANTING]
天哪
My, what interesting decor.
多有趣的布置
I knew you'd love it.
我就知道你会喜欢
Don't ask.
不要问
MARLENE: There we go.
ALBIN: Yes, I was out riding today.
给你
对 我今天骑马外出了
JONAS: Well, I think that it's gonna be
quite a bit easier now that....
呃 我想现在会更容易点...
哇
Whoa.
[GLASS SHATTERS]
Look, the Odd Squad is staring.
看 怪人队在盯着
Pretend they're not there.
假装他们不在那儿
[GLASS SHATTERS]
-Ugh.
-Oh! I love this song. Marie, come dance with me.
我爱这首歌！玛丽 来跟我跳舞！
[DANCE MUSIC
PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS]
[GIRLS LAUGHING]
Hey, nerd girl, you weren't too bad
at dressage trials today.
嗨 电脑呆妹 今天盛装舞步赛不赖嘛
Thanks. Boy, that first prize is heavy.
多谢 哥们 第一名沉甸甸啊
Yeah, yeah, you got lucky.
对对 走运
呃 想跳舞吗？
You wanna dance?
I wouldn't wanna step
on your little second-place feet.
我不想踩到你的第二名小脚脚
I'll take a chance.
我冒冒险
[GLASS SHATTERS]
-Whoa. What were the odds of that?
-You didn't see that coming?
哇 怪人们在干什么？
没看见吗？
你在喝我的潘趣酒 你这塞满酸菜的香肠！
That is my punch you are drinking,
you stuffed sauerkraut sausage.
Ugh! It is mine, you pompous pickled pudding.
是我的 你这自大的腌布丁！
-Creampuff.
-Bonbon for brains.
奶油泡芙！
巧克力糖！
PHILIPPE: Chocolate mousse.
-I think I'm losing my appetite.
巧克力慕斯！
我想我没胃口了
[NEIGHING]
Oh, Stacie, I'm just going out to the corral.
斯塔西 我去畜栏看看
Yeah, yeah, that's nice. Have fun.
好好 那很好 玩的开心
CHELSEA:
I'll be right back.
我就回来
Yaah! Ooh!
[NEIGHING]
Aah! Whoa! Aah!
Uhn! Uhn! Whoa! Aah!
[CHELSEA SCREAMING]
- Chelsea.
-Chelsea.
切尔西！
- 切尔西？
- 切尔西！
Chelsea.
[CHELSEA SCREAMING]
Chelsea! Hold on.
切尔西！
- Chelsea.
STACIE: Chelsea, hold on.
抓紧 切尔西！
艾蒂安！
BARBIE:
Hang on, Chelsea.
ALL:
Chelsea!
切尔西！
BARBIE: Chelsea.
SKIPPER: Chelsea.
- 切尔西？
- Chelsea, are you okay?
STACIE: Chelsea, are you okay?
切尔西 能听见我吗？
MARLENE:
Can you hear me?
BARBIE: Chelse.
-Dash. Oh. Ooh, ha-ha.
切儿...
点点！停！
Stop. I'm okay.
我没事
[ALL SIGH]
She's okay. Just a little shaken. She'll be fine.
她没事 只是有点受惊 她会好起来的
- Chelsea, why on Earth--?
-I just wanted to ride a big horse...
切尔西 到底为什么？
我只是想骑大马
像和芭比和斯塔西那样
...like you and Barbie and Stacie do.
Oh, Chelsea, I think you've done
quite enough riding for one day.
哦 切尔西
我想一天已经骑得够多了
Let's get you inside.
让我们带进去
And, Etienne, we'll need to get a doctor
to look at your arm.
艾蒂安 我们需要请医生看看你胳膊
Thank goodness she's okay.
But what about our horses?
谢天谢地她没事
但我们马怎么办？它们都跑了
They're all gone.
The race. We must go after them.
比赛！我们必须去追它们！
How? It's dark and we don't know
which way they went.
怎么追？天黑了 我们不知道它们去哪里了
JONAS:
I can track them.
我能追踪它们
Jonas, you know how to do that?
乔纳斯 你知道怎么做？
I know these hills like Skipper knows her tablet.
我熟悉这山区 就像斯基珀熟悉她的平板
My friends said we could use their horses.
我朋友说我们能用他们的马
- Let's go.
-We'll call the neighbouring farms...
我们出发！
我们能打电话给附近农场请他们留意逃走的马
...and ask them to keep a lookout
for the runaways.
我来帮忙！
CHELSEA:
I'll help.
[CHUCKLES]
[ANIMAL HOOTING]
Come on. This way.
快 这边！
JONAS: Hmm.
BARBIE: What is it?
- 嗯
- 怎么了？
JONAS:
These tracks.
这些足迹...
You see that set of prints?
看见这蹄印了吗？
That horse is coming from a different direction
than the others.
这马来自与其它马不同的方向
然后它在这儿加入了其它马
- Then it joins the rest here.
SKIPPER: Huh.
嗯 它没有戴马掌
- It's not wearing horseshoes.
JONAS: Exactly.
正是 然后看起来它领马群往那方向去了
Then it appears to lead the herd away
in that direction.
JONAS:
I'm afraid that's it.
恐怕没办法了
The prints lead onto these rocks
and then vanish.
蹄印走到岩石上就消失了
-Sorry.
-Now what?
对不起
现在怎么办？比赛几小时内就开始
高山学校却没有马
The race is in a few hours
and A|pine's got no horses.
Aunt Marlene might as well
kiss the school goodbye.
玛琳姨妈可能要和学校吻别了
Wait, I know where they might be.
等等！我知道它们可能在哪！
[NEIGHING]
Good job, Majesty.
做得好 真命天女！
I wonder if she babysits. Four sugar cubes
an hour and all the hay she can eat.
我想知道她做不做保姆
每小时四块糖 干草随便吃
That horse...
那匹马...
...the one with the pink mane.
有粉红鬃毛的那匹
是什么品种？
-What breed is it?
-A very special one.
非常特别的品种
And they're our secret. Okay?
它们是我们的秘密 好吗？
Looks like the steeplechase is still on.
看起来越野障碍赛跑还有戏！
[NEIGHING]
Monsieur Philippe. What a pleasant surprise.
菲利普先生 真是喜相逢
You think you're very clever, don't you?
And you. Traitor. Turncoat.
以为很聪明 是不是？还有你！叛徒！崇奸！
Do not bother returning to L'Ecole.
别想回崇山学校了！
Mam'se||e Barbie, I owe you a debt of gratitude.
芭比小姐 我欠人情
I believe you have found a place
I have searched for since I was a child...
我相信找到了我从小就开始搜寻的地方...
...The Valley of the Majestiques.
真命天马峡谷
BARB I E:
Majestiques?
真命天马？但是先生 你说它们只是童话故事！
-But, monsieur, you said they were fairy tales.
PHILIPPE: Ha!
那是为我哥哥好
That was for my brother's benefit.
[CHUCKLES]
I have always known they were real
and worth a king's ransom.
我一直知道它们是真的 值得千金买骨
And now I know they are somewhere
on Alpine land.
现在 我知道它们在高山学校某地
As you've said, this is Alpine land.
正如你所言 这是高山学校的地
Well, after today's race,
this land will belong to Ecole Montagne...
好 今天比赛后 这地就属于崇山学校了
马上我有的是时间找到它们
...and soon I will have all the time in the world
to find them.
Unless, of course, Monsieur Etienne
leaves you in the dust.
除非 当然 艾蒂安先生让你吃灰尘
Oh, didn't you hear'? My brother's broken arm
will keep him from riding.
你们没听说吗？我哥哥胳膊断了 比不了赛
SKIPPER: What?
PHILIPPE: But do not worry.
但不用担心 一旦这地归我了
Once this land is mine,
I may let you look at the Majestiques for a price.
我可以让你们看真命天马...
出大价钱
[LAUGHING]
We have to win that race.
我们必须赢得这场比赛
ANNOUNCER:
Day two of the tournament...
锦标赛第二天
...and we're here at Bernwald Racetrack
for the concluding event...
我们来到柏瓦德赛道进行最后的项目
...the annual 3.2 kilometre steeplechase.
年度3.2公里越野障碍赛跑
Alpine Academy and Ecole Montagne
are tied going into the race.
高山学校和崇山学校不分上下进入比赛
Aren't Barbie and Skipper coming?
芭比和斯基珀怎么还不来？
They'll make it here in time. I just know it.
她们会及时赶到的！我就知道！
ANNOUNCER:
Riding for Centre Equestre, Jason Randall.
代表马术中心的杰森・兰德尔
Riding for Ecole Montagne,
Monsieur Philippe Cheynet on Hurricane.
代表崇山学校的
骑飓风的菲利普・谢内先生！
[GROWLING]
You lose again, Etienne.
你又输了 艾蒂安！
[LAUGHING]
ANNOUNCER:
Ladies and gentlemen, an announcement.
女士们先生们 特此宣告
高山学校今年不参加赛跑
Alpine academy will not be racing this year.
- I'm sorry, Marlene.
-We tried our best.
我很抱歉 玛琳
我们尽力了
ANNOUNCER:
--the registration is now....
时间到了 登记现在...
Wait a moment. There's a late entry.
等等！有人姗姗来迟！
Riding for Alpine is Barbie Roberts on Majesty.
代表高山学校的
骑真命天女的芭比・罗伯茨！
[BOTH GASP]
[CHATTERING]
[GASPS]
艾蒂安！那是...
MARLENE: Etienne. ls that--?
-Yes, a Majestique.
对
一匹真命天马
Easy now. Easy. The saddle's not so bad.
放松 现在放松
马鞍不是这么坏 会习惯它的
You'll get used to it.
[NEIGHING]
停 没事的 真命天女
Whoa. It's okay, Majesty.
That's a beautiful horse, Ms. Roberts.
靓马 罗伯茨小姐 不久它就不属于了
It will not be yours much longer.
We will see, monsieur.
我们走着瞧 先生
Wow. It's like they're real.
哇！栩栩如生！
ANNOUNCER:
Riders, ready.
骑手准备！
The wire is up. And they're off!
时间到 出发！
[CROWD CHEERING]
[NEIGHING]
Easy, girl, easy. It's all right.
放松 放松 没关系
老师宠儿一马当先
首席女歌手紧跟其后 好样的第三！
ANNOUNCER:
Teacher's Pet takes the lead.
Way To Go in third.
Majesty is rearing out the gate.
真命天女在门口直立不前
[MAJESTY NEIGHING]
That's it. Settle. It's okay. Hyah!
就这样 镇定 没关系
驾！
[CROWD CHEERING]
Come on, Majesty. You can do it.
快 真命天女 能做到！
ANNOUNCER:
Way To Go moving into the number two spot...
好样的跻身第二
...as riders head for the first water ditch.
在骑手们冲向第一道水沟的时候！
拉可雷特坠马了！
Raclette is down.
You can do this, girl.
It's just like the glacier streams.
能做到 姑娘！这就跟冰河一样！
Go Mam'seI/e Barbie, go, go!
Go, Barbie!
我们爱 芭比！
ANNOUNCER: Rounding the turn to jump four,
it's Cr茅me Br铿l茅e and Way To Go leading...
风水轮流转 四号障碍是焦糖奶油和
好样的领先 首席女歌手落后
...with Prima Donna dropping back,
followed by Teacher's Pet with Hurricane gaining.
老师宠儿紧跟 飓风在加速
[NEIGHING]
天哪 老师宠儿甩掉了骑手！
Teacher's Pet has spilled its rider.
PHILIPPE:
Go, you mangy beast!
快走 你这个脏畜生！
ANNOUNCER: Hurricane passes Prima Donna
and challenges Creme Br铿l茅e for second
飓风超过首席女歌手 马上要挑战焦糖奶油
在他们跳过树篱的时候
...as they come to the Hedge Jump.
Majesty still trailing in last place.
真命天女仍然在最后一名尾追
[NEIGHING]
[CROWD GASPS]
What's this? Cr茅me Br铿l茅e, is out of the race.
怎么回事？焦糖奶油退出了比赛！
That is just plain wrong.
Come on, Majesty, let's show him.
真不道德 快 真命天女 我们秀给他看！
延后发力 真命天女火箭般超过了首席女歌手！
ANNOUNCER: Making a late charge,
Majesty rockets to overtake Prima Donna.
Way To Go in first.
好样的位居第一 骑真命天女的芭比・罗伯茨
Barbie Roberts on Majesty
continues a spectacular come from behind...
继续迅猛后来居上
...challenging reigning champion
Philippe Cheynet on Hurricane for second.
马上就要挑战现任冠军骑飓风的菲利普・谢内！
[BARBIE SCREAMS THEN MAJESTIC NEIGHS]
Barbie Roberts is down.
The saddle's come off her horse.
芭比・罗伯茨坠马了！她马的马鞍松了！
看上去罗伯茨小姐和真命天女退出了比赛！
It looks like Miss Roberts and Majesty
are out of the race.
[GRUNTS]
He can't stop us. Come on, Majesty.
他不能让我们停步 来 真命天女
Born free, ride free.
生得自由 骑得自由！
[NEIGHING]
飓风现在逼近好样的
ANNOUNCER:
Hurricane now closing in on Way To Go.
PHILIPPE:
Hyah!
[NEIGHING]
ANNOUNCER:
Hurricane and Way To Go are neck and neck.
飓风和好样的并驾齐驱
Oh, Way To Go stumbles.
好样的马失前蹄！
Way To Go at the inside fence
refusing the jump.
好样的在篱笆内拒绝起跳
Philippe Cheynet now firmly in first place.
菲利普・谢内现在铁定第一
Just one more jump before another victory
for Ecole Montagne.
只要再一跳 崇山学校就又赢了
Alpine and the Majestiques are mine.
高山学校和真命天马是我的！
ANNOUNCER: Wait a moment. Barbie Roberts
is back in the race and gaining fast.
等等 芭比・罗伯茨又回到比赛急起直追！
Philippe Cheynet takes the jump.
What's this? Unbelievable.
菲利普・谢内起跳！
什么？不敢相信！
[ALL CHEERING]
Yaah! Whoo-hoo!
芭比・罗伯茨和真命天女最后冲刺！
[ANNOUNCER TALKING INDISTINCTLY]
菲利普・谢内怒气冲冲想重新领先
真命天女和飓风在最后冲刺！
[NEIGHS]
[SCREAMS]
ANNOUNCER: And the winner for Alpine Academy
is Barbie Roberts on Majesty!
获胜者是高山学校骑真命天女的芭比・罗伯茨！
[NEIGHING]
[COUGHS]
[LAUGHS THEN PANTS]
You did it, Majesty. You did it.
做到了 真命天女 做到了！
[NEIGHING]
ANNOUNCER:
Ladies and gentlemen.
女士们先生们！锦标赛总冠军属于
The overall Tournament Cup goes
to Alpine Equestrian Academy.
高山马术学校！
[ALL CHEERING]
It is an outrage. I should have won that race.
气死我了！我本该赢得比赛的！
I was unfairly distracted.
我被不公平的分心了！
Hmm. By what? Your own cheating?
被什么分心？你自己的作弊？
We saw what you did, you penguin's patoot.
我们看见你干的了 你这个企鹅屁股！
And you are the lint in a baboon's belly button.
你是狒狒肚脐眼上的毛球！
Ah. Here we go again.
又来了
[WOMAN SPEAKS IN FRENCH]
- (法语)住口！
- 嗷！
Aah! Hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo!
Now go to your room. You are on le time-out.
现在去你房间！面壁思过！
But, maman, he started it.
但是妈妈！他先开始的！
[LAUGHING]
You were magnifique.
是真命天马！
呃 谢谢 呃...
Thank you.
Madame Cheynet,
the owner of Ecole Montagne.
谢内夫人 崇山学校所有者
Bridgette, I won't be needing to sell Alpine.
布丽奇特 我不用卖掉高山学校了
[SPEAKING IN FRENCH]
恭喜 玛琳
I am most happy for you.
我真为们高兴
[ETIENNE SPEAKS IN FRENCH]
妈妈...
-This horse, the legend.
-I know.
这马...是传奇
我知道 她真漂亮
Isn't she beautiful?
Come, mon chouchou. I made soup.
来 我亲爱的 我做了汤
Do I get a baguette this time?
这次我有长棍面包了？
[CROWD CHEERING AND APPLAUDING]
Thank you. I love it.
谢谢 我喜欢
Uhn. Here's Stacie's last bag.
这是斯塔西最后的包
爆米花花和我将她其余的东西都打包好了
Popcorn and I packed the rest of her stuff.
Hey, where is Popcorn?
嗨 爆米花花在哪里？
[BARKING]
喔
Oh. Heh.
Well, I think that's everything.
好 我想东西齐了
I just wanna thank you again, Aunt Marlene.
我只想再次感谢 玛琳姨妈
This has been the best summer ever.
这是我曾有过的最棒的夏日
No, I thank all of you.
不 我感谢们大家
Once Skipper posted her video of the race online,
our enrolment tripled.
自从斯基珀发布了比赛视频
我们的入学人数涨了三倍！
我想我们的学校将日久天长
I think we will be teaching riders
for many years to come.
At school, I signed up a whole bunch
of students for riding...
在学校 我收了一大堆学生
学骑马的 学盛装舞步的
...and dressage lessons...
还有个想学弹班卓琴的 总之我也收了他
...and one wants to learn to play the banjo,
but I signed him up anyway.
[SIGHS]
[JONAS GRUNTING]
- Well, that's the last of it.
-Thanks for helping.
好 这是最后一件了
多谢帮忙 你不是个坏小子！有时
You're not a bad guy sometimes.
Careful, you almost said something nice to me.
小心 几乎在跟我说友好话了
And since you like marshmallow shampoo
so much...
既然这么喜欢棉花糖香波
我会寄给我的第二最爱 棉花糖饼干香水
...I'm gonna send you my next favourite,
Scent Aux S'mores.
Yeah, me too.
And I'm sorry about all the things I said.
对 我也是 我很抱歉我说过的那些话
You really are a great pony. And just my size.
真是一匹好小马 正合我的尺寸
Okay, I admit it. I'm gonna miss you.
好 我承认 我会想念
Even though you gave my sister years' worth
of embarrassing pictures of me...
尽管让我姐姐拍下我几年来最尴尬照片
...you're still a very cool horse.
仍然是一匹非常酷的马
[NEIGHING]
[CHUCKLES]
See you in Malibu, Majesty.
马里布见 真命天女 我想会喜欢加州
I think you're gonna like California.
You've chosen an amazing horse, Barbie.
选了一匹好马 芭比
I'm certain that you and she
will win many, many races together.
我肯定和她会一起赢得很多很多场比赛
[HORSE NEIGHING]
[NEIGHING]
MARLENE: Barbie, aren't you excited?
-No.
芭比？难道不激动吗？
不 不 我不会那么做
No, I won't do it.
-Barbie, what are you doing?
-Letting her go.
芭比 在干嘛？
让她走 我不能那样 玛琳姨妈 我就是不能
I can't, Aunt Marlene, I just can't.
She belongs here with her family.
她属于这儿她的家
I could never take that away from her.
我决不能夺走她的家
That decision comes from your heart.
I think it's the right one.
这决定发自的内心 我想下对了
Mm. I'll never forget you. Never.
我绝不会忘记 绝不会 现在走吧
Now go.
If you come back, I know she will come back.
如果回来 我知道她也会回来
[HORN HONKING]
SKIPPER:
Come on, Barbie.
快点 芭比！
This thing won't drive itself.
这玩意可不会自己开！
[BARNABY BLEATS]
ALL:
Bye!
[YELLING INDISTINCTLY]
[POPCORN BARKING]
MARIE:
Bye, Barbie!
[NEIGHING]
BARBIE:
Okay, now, who's got the boarding passes?
好 谁拿了登机牌？
[BLEATING]
《你是缘》 演唱：海薇・盖茨
"You're The One" performed by Heavynn Gates
[HEAVYNN GATES' "YOU'RE THE ONE"
PLAYING]
有人说 你不能被发现
Some people say you can't be found
你不在身边
You're not around
哦 哦 哦 哦 哦
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
有人说 你不真实
Some people say that you're not real
童话故事
A fairytale
有人说 你不真实
Some people say that you're not real
童话故事
A fairytale
哦 哦 哦 哦 哦
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
童话故事
A fairytale
哦 哦 哦 哦 哦
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
他们说梦是用来酣眠
They say that dreams are for sleepin'
我完全清醒抱着信念
I'm wide awake and believin'
张开眼 我看见
Open my eyes and see
我完全清醒抱着信念
I'm wide awake and believin'
张开眼 我看见
Open my eyes and see
你就在 我眼前
You're right in front of me
你是缘
You're the one
我一直知道
I've known all along
你是缘
You're the one
你是全部我想要
You're all that I want
你是缘
You're the one
你是全部我想要
You're all that I want
你豪情无限 为我撑起天
You're wild and free, strong enough for me
我们结下的缘将沧海桑田
And what we have will never be undone
哦 哦 哦 你是缘
Oh, ooh, ooh, you're the one
我听见你声音 尽在不言
I hear your voice without a word
灵犀一点
It's understood
哦 哦 哦 哦 哦
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
有一些事 我们皆知
There's something here and we both know
去做的方式
The way to go
有一些事 我们皆知
There's something here and we both know
去做的方式
The way to go
哦 哦 哦 哦 哦
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
他们说梦是用来酣眠
They say that dreams are for sleepin'
我完全清醒抱着信念
I'm wide awake and believin'
张开眼 我看见
Open my eyes and see
你就在 我眼前
You're right in front of me
你是缘
You're the one
你就在 我眼前
You're right in front of me
你是缘
You're the one
我一直知道
I've known all along
你是缘
You're the one
我一直知道
I've known all along
你是缘
You're the one
你是全部我想要
You're all that I want
你豪情无限 为我撑起天
You're wild and free, strong enough for me
你是全部我想要
You're all that I want
你豪情无限 为我撑起天
You're wild and free, strong enough for me
我们结下的缘将沧海桑田
And what we have will never be undone
哦 哦 哦 你是缘
Oh, ooh, ooh, you're the one
我们结下的缘将沧海桑田
And what we have will never be undone
哦 哦 哦 你是缘
Oh, ooh, ooh, you're the one
像每天破晓的光线
Like the morning each dawn
你保持我心坚
You keep me holding on
陪我一路远
Run away with me
你为我一路牵
The way you are to me
你教我如何看明天
You show me how to see tomorrow
明天
Tomorrow
你是缘
You're the one
我一直知道
I've known all along
你是缘
You're the one
你是全部我想要
You're all that I want
你是缘
You're the one...
你是缘(像每天破晓的光线)
You're the one(like the morning each dawn)
(你保持我心坚)(你是缘)
(You keep me holding on)(You're the one)
你是缘(像每天破晓的光线)
You're the one(like the morning each dawn)
(你保持我心坚)(你是缘)
(You keep me holding on)(You're the one)
你是缘
You're the one
我一直知道
I've known all along
你是缘(你为我一路牵)
You're the one (the way you are to me)
我一直知道
I've known all along
你是缘(你为我一路牵)
You're the one (the way you are to me)
(你教我如何看明天)(你是缘)
(You show me how to see)(You're the one)
你是缘
You're the one
你是全部我想要
You're all that I want
你豪情无限 为我撑起天
You're wild and free, strong enough for me
我们结下的缘将沧海桑田
And what we have will never be undone
哦 哦 哦 你是缘
Oh, ooh, ooh. You're the one
“如果你爱什么，让它自由”
――芭比